<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TextSummarizer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>


    <string-array name="type_names">
        <item>Select Type</item>
        <item>Textbook</item>
        <item>Cooking</item>
        <item>Science</item>
        <item>Animal</item>
        <item>News</item>
        <item>Leisure</item>
        <item>Technology</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="empty"></string>
    <string name="invalid_url">Can\'t open the URL.\nPlease try with a valid URL</string>
    <string name="is_saved">Article is saved</string>
    <string name="is_unsaved">Article is unsaved</string>
    <string name="not_implemented">This function is not implemented yet</string>

    <string name="sample1_url">https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/whos-who-in-the-george-papadopoulos-court-documents/2017/10/30/e131158c-bdb3-11e7-97d9-bdab5a0ab381_story.html?utm_term=.be7f3dfd193d</string>
    <string name="sample1_favicon_path">drawable/wp_favicon</string>
    <string name="sample1_author">Rosalind S. Helderman</string>
    <string name="sample1_title">Who’s who in the George Papadopoulos court documents</string>
    <string name="sample1_text">
        <![CDATA[Newly released court documents show that Trump foreign policy adviser
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?q=George+Papadopoulos&rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&oq=George+Papadopoulos&aqs=chrome..69i57.1828j0j9&sourceid=chrome&ie=UTF-8">George Papadopoulos</a>
        communicated with several senior campaign officials about his outreach to the Russian government over a period of months. The recipients of
        Papadopoulos\'s emails are not named in the filings,
        but The Washington Post has identified several individuals based on interviews and other documents.
        Papadopoulos pleaded guilty this month to lying to federal agents about his outreach to Russia.
        “The Campaign Supervisor”: Trump campaign national co-chairman
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?q=Sam+Clovis&rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&oq=Sam+Clovis&aqs=chrome..69i57.808j0j4&sourceid=chrome&ie=UTF-8">Sam Clovis</a>
        Victoria Toensing, an attorney for Sam Clovis, confirmed that several references in court filings
        to “the campaign supervisor” refer to the onetime radio host from Iowa, who served as
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&ei=c98uWouKGNGvggerprPwDw&q=Trump">Trump</a>\'s
        national campaign co-chairman. At one point, Papadopoulos emailed Clovis and other campaign
        officials about a March 24, 2016, meeting he had in London with a professor, who had introduced
        him to the Russian ambassador and a Russian woman he described as “
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&ei=298uWt2YJoj4_Aah7KuABA&q=Putin">Putin</a>\’s niece.”
        The group had talked about arranging a meeting “between us and the Russian leadership to
            discuss U.S.-Russia ties under President Trump,” Papadopoulos wrote.]]>
             </string>
    <string name="sample1_source">WashingtonPost</string>
    <string name="sample1_image_path">drawable/wp_image</string>


    <string name="sample2_url">"http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-middle-east-42250399</string>
    <string name="sample2_favicon_path">drawable/bbc_favicon</string>
    <string name="sample2_author">BBC News</string>
    <string name="sample2_title">US Jerusalem recognition \'kiss of death\'</string>
    <string name="sample2_text">
        <![CDATA[An expected announcement by President
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&ei=8t8uWvKeG8q0_AbmjI_oDg&q=Donald+Trump">Donald Trump</a>
        that the US will become the first country to recognise
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&ei=cOAuWoLPGMvk_QbbrKHgDQ&q=Jerusalem">Jerusalem</a> as
        Israel\'s capital has been dubbed a "kiss of death" for the Middle East peace process by the
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&ei=1-AuWsrqJ8_w_AaG87voBw&q=Palestinians">Palestinians</a>. But an Israeli
        minister urged other countries to follow the US lead. Mr Trump is expected to confirm the decision in a speech later.
        Pope Francis called for the status quo in Jerusalem to be respected, in line with United Nations resolutions.
        Mr Trump will also start the process of moving the US embassy from Tel Aviv to Jerusalem.
        The decision - which would fulfil a campaign promise and appeal to Mr Trump\'s right-wing base - risks
        a heated reaction from US allies in the Muslim world and brings a risk of protests and unrest. It also
        makes it difficult for the US to be seen as a neutral mediator in the Middle East peace process.
        East Jerusalem was annexed from Jordan after the 1967 war in the Middle East, and is not recognised
        by other countries as part of Israel. Israel has always regarded Jerusalem as its capital,
        while the Palestinians want East Jerusalem to be the capital of a future Palestinian state.
        In recognising Jerusalem as Israel\'s capital, the US would be reversing its own longstanding policy
        that the status of the holy city would need to be resolved as part of Middle East peace talks.
        The Palestinians' representative to the UK,
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&ei=C-EuWvzJDayH_Qao5KqIAQ&q=Manuel+Hassassian">Manuel Hassassian</a>, told the BBC that the changes
        to US policy on Jerusalem amounted to a "kiss of death" for the two-state solution in peace
        efforts and were like a "declaration of war". Israeli Education Minister
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&ei=WuEuWtewKouU_QaomL74DA&q=Naftali+Bennett">Naftali Bennett</a> described
        it as a "big step towards regional peace" and said other countries should move their embassies too.
        Theresa May said she would speak to Mr Trump about the US move. The UK's position on Jerusalem had not
        changed, the Prime Minister told Parliament. The city's status should be the subject of negotiation and
        it should be the shared capital of Israel and a Palestinian state, she added. Turkey's President Recep
        Tayyip Erdogan said the step would "play into the hands of terror groups". The BBC's Barbara Plett-Usher,
        in Washington, says the president is expected to try and calm international alarm by stating that the US
        is prepared to support a two-state solution, if both Israelis and Palestinians agree to it.]]>
    </string>
    <string name="sample2_source">BBC News</string>
    <string name="sample2_image_path">drawable/bbc_image</string>


    <string name="sample3_url">"http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-42256140</string>
    <string name="sample3_favicon_path">drawable/bbc_favicon</string>
    <string name="sample3_author">BBC News</string>
    <string name="sample3_title">Putin to run again for Russia president</string>
    <string name="sample3_text">
        <![CDATA[Russia\'s
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&ei=298uWt2YJoj4_Aah7KuABA&q=Putin">Vladimir Putin</a> has
        said he will seek another term as president in next year\'s election.
        He made the announcement in a speech to workers at a car factory in the Volga city of
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&ei=MOIuWsaVLcO7ggfNtIegDQ&q=Nizhny+Novgorod">Nizhny Novgorod</a>.
        "I will put forward my candidacy for the post of president of the Russian federation," he said.
        Mr Putin has been in power since 2000, either as president or prime minister. If he wins the March
        election he will be eligible to serve until 2024. Russian TV journalist Ksenia Sobchak has already
        said she will stand in the election but opinion polls suggest Mr Putin will win easily. Russia\'s main
        opposition leader,
        <a href="https://www.google.com/search?rlz=1C1CHBF_enUS748US748&ei=mOEuWvKlJa7G_Qbv2LeQAQ&q=Alexei+Navalny">Alexei Navalny</a>,
        has been formally barred from standing because he was found guilty
        of embezzlement - a charge he claims was politically motivated. Mr Putin is popular with many Russians,
        who see him as a strong leader who has restored Russia's global standing with a decisive military intervention
        in the Syrian civil war and Russia's annexation of Crimea from Ukraine. But his critics accuse him of
        facilitating corruption and illegally annexing Crimea, which has led to international condemnation.]]>
    </string>
    <string name="sample3_source">BBC News</string>
    <string name="sample3_image_path">drawable/bbc_image1</string>


    <string name="password_sent">Password reset information sent to email</string>
    <string name="signed_out">Successfully signed out</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Signed in as</string>

</resources>
